Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.10.31 10:53:43
-=The Last Fantasy=-
翻译:雪梨，sindouhikaru，Pooh，哈拉尔，Anya 校对:岁月倒影，TYY
（学校选举）
（本周学校选举）
（选举登记处）
Hey, Sasha, say something presidential.
Whoa, Chloe, slow down. The election hasn't even started yet.
What do you think Sasha's chances are?
Well, she knows the most about student government, she's worked her way up...
...she's on a ton of committees, but she's more of a worker than a leader.
How about Paul?
He's certainly the most qualified...
...but elections aren't about merit, they're about popularity.
Which brings us to Felice.
Head cheerleader and president of the drama club.
That definitely gives her an edge, not to mention that she's really hot.
Yeah, but her name rhymes with the French word for luggage.
Okay, glad to see you're not reaching for reasons to hate her.
I saw you taking Sasha's picture.
Why haven't you taken mine? That qualifies as biased.
I plan on running photos and bios of all the candidates, including you, Felice.
Hey, Chloe, what about the editorial?
You can only endorse one candidate, so who's it gonna be?
Who cares? No matter what she says, people are gonna vote for me.
Never underestimate the need for the clinically ambitious to pad their resumes.
You want to avoid the pain and humiliation of losing?
Drop out now.
Ow!
片名:超人前传
主题曲《Save me》:谁来拯救我
领衔主演：汤姆・威灵
让你温暖的手伸出驱散我的痛苦
主演:克丽斯汀・克鲁克
谁来拯救我
主演:迈克尔・罗森巴姆
我不在乎你是怎么做到
主演：埃里克・约翰森
只要你留下，和我在一起
主演：山姆・琼斯三世
快来吧，我一直在等待着你
主演：艾利森・麦克
主演：安妮特・奥图尔
约翰・施耐得 饰演 强纳森・肯特
我一直留着整个世界只为你闪耀
超人始创作者:杰瑞・希杰尔和乔・夏斯特
留下，留下
快出现吧
电视策划:阿尔弗雷德・哥夫，麦尔斯・米莱
第十八集:雄蜂
萨莎，用主席口吻说点儿什么
克罗伊，急什么，竞选还没开始呢
你认为萨莎的优势在哪？
她熟悉学生管理工作，一心向上爬…
…参加了很多社团组织 但是比起当领导，她更适合实干
那保罗呢？
毫无疑问，他是最有资格的…
但竞选最讲究的不是人的价值，而是知名度
所以要看佛丽丝了
啦啦队长兼戏剧社主席
无疑让她占了优势，何况她还是个辣妹
但她的名字和法语的“行李”一个调
好吧，很高兴你不是在找借口讨厌她
我刚看到你给萨莎拍照
为什么没有给我拍？对我有偏见吧
我打算把所有候选人的照片和履历汇编成册 也包括你，佛丽丝
克罗伊，那社论呢？
你只能支持一个候选人，会是谁？
谁在乎？不管她说什么 人们都会投票给我的
有人为了填充简历，还真是野心勃勃
如果不想尝到失败的痛苦和屈辱
现在就退出吧
（我会为你而战，陈保罗）
那真是我最可怕的噩梦
That's gotta be my all-time worst nightmare.
特别客串主演:玛格丽特・莫罗
I get stung by one bee, I swell up like a grapefruit, but over a hundred....
客串主演:尚达・法
How'd they get into Paul's bathroom?
曾经被一只蜜蜂蛰，就肿得跟西柚一样 如果有成百上千只的话…
关键是它们怎么飞进保罗浴室的？
切兰・西蒙斯
The Center for Environmental Protection...
环保中心…
…从大都市派了小组来调查
...is sending a team from Metropolis to investigate.
神川宏奈幸
Guess that's gonna shake up our class election.
我猜肯定会让选举结果大变
不会，我是说，保罗的名字还在候选名单上…
Not really. I mean, Paul's name is still on the ballot...
…到秋天才要就职，那时他应该已经好了
...and he wouldn't take office until fall. He could recover by then.
监督制片:马克・伏黑顿
Out of sight, out of mind.
久别情疏
要我说，他只能得到几张同情票
My call, he gets a few sympathy votes. That's it.
制片人:迈克尔・格林
-Nice to see the softer side of Pete. -Seriously.
制片人:道里斯・伊根
Anyway, there's a new candidate on the horizon who is gonna make things interesting.
- 很高兴看到皮特心软的一面 - 是啊
不管怎样，眼前就有个新候选人 有他在，会很有趣的
是吗，那是谁呢？
Oh, yeah, who's that?
（克拉克・肯特竞选主席）
- 你干了什么？ - 我从你身上预见到很好的政治前景
-What have you done? -I see a big future ahead of you in politics.
联合制片:格雷格・沃克
你坦率正直，受人喜爱
You're straightforward. People like you.
- 不行，肯定不行 - 你具备所有条件
-No way. Definitely not. -You've got the whole package:
制片人:鲍勃・哈格罗夫
Looks, brains, and that whole farm-boy charm.
Did I mention the perks of power?
-lf it was so great, why didn't you run? -I know my strengths.
I'm more the power behind the throne.
The guy behind the guy. The one who makes it all happen.
-Pete Ross, the kingmaker. -Exactly.
All you gotta do is show up, shake a couple hands, give a speech. It's easy.
And we wonder why our politicians aren't great leaders.
Clark, Clark, Clark, Clark....
联合执行制片:肯・霍顿
外表，头脑，还有农场男孩的魅力
我刚还漏说了超大力这一点
- 既然主席那么好，你怎么不去竞选？ - 我有自知之明
我更适合做权力背后的人
成功人士背后的支持者 帮别人把成功成为实现的人
- 皮特・罗斯，国王拥立者 - 完全正确
你只要露个面，挥挥手，做个演讲，很容易
真奇怪为何我们的政治家还不是伟大领导人
克拉克，克拉克…
编剧:迈克尔・格林，菲利普・莱温斯
导演:迈克尔・卡特曼
- 看来你需要帮助 - 不，我能搞定
-You look like you could use some help. -No, I'm fine.
汉斯，我要你到90号路，公馆东面两英里
Hans, I need you out on Route 90, two miles east of the mansion.
- 一辆红色野马车引擎出问题了 - 你这是干什么？
-A red Mustang with engine trouble. -What are you doing?
打电话给我修车工
Calling my mechanic.
不是我不欣赏你的现代骑士精神 但我说过自己能搞定
Not that I don't appreciate your attempt at postmodern chivalry, but I said I was fine.
穿D&G，谈吐文雅
Dolce & Gabbana and a vocabulary?
你的言行完全是大都会的风格 怎么会来斯摩维尔？
You've got Metropolis written all over you. What brings you to Smallville?
你是来赶我走的警察吗？
You're the sheriff come to run me out of town?
你的态度是跟这身衣服一套的？还是点缀？
Did the attitude come with the couture, or was it an accessory?
既然你非问不可，我正考虑搬来这儿
If you must know, I'm thinking about moving here.
我想打听下这里情况，但你看着不像本地人
I'd ask you what it's like, but you don't look like a local.
我从去年秋天起就住这儿 起初迫切地想走，但后来越住越融入
I've lived here since last fall. I couldn't wait to get out, but it's growing on me.
为什么会改变？ 这里诺曼洛克维尔的格调诱惑了你？
Well, why the change? The Norman Rockwell ambiance seduce you?
外表只是假象，这儿所有东西都另有故事
Appearance is deceptive. Nothing around here is what it seems.
吊人胃口啊，是什么意思？
I'm intrigued. What do you mean?
这些问题听着有点像采访了
All these questions. This is beginning to sound like an interview.
- 你给谁做事？ - 不知道你在说什么
-Who do you work for? -I don't know what you're talking about.
如果我把它扔进林子，你就真需要一辆拖车了
If I toss these into the woods, you really are gonna need a tow truck.
凯瑞・卡索，我是《大都会日报》的记者
Carrie Castle. I'm a staff reporter for the Metropolis Journal.
我不接受采访，卡索小姐
I don't grant interviews, Ms. Castle.
我大半辈子都在躲着你们这种人
I've spent most of my life taking back entrances to avoid people like you.
等一下，听我说，我想为你写篇专访
Wait. Just listen. I want to write an article about you.
你就靠这句话打动我？写我的文章多了去了
That's your pitch? There are articles written about me all the time.
但在那些文章里，您不是被开除的小混混 就是莱诺・卢瑟被宠坏的儿子
But you're either dismissed as a wild child or the spoiled son of Lionel Luthor.
虽然您在《询查报》那里挽回了些许名声…
You've gotten some good press in the Inquisitor...
但我们的报纸不是那种街头小报，我们受尊重 能帮助您改善形象
...but the Journal is not a tabloid. It's respected. It could help change your image.
- 你有什么想法？ - 写一篇封面报道描述您在斯摩维尔的工作
-What did you have in mind? -A cover profile on your work in Smallville.
那篇文章会保持公允…
It will be fair and accurate...
…同时帮您适当摆脱父亲的阴影
...and will give you the legitimacy you need to get out of your father's shadow.
推动我事业的同时宣传你自己
Launching my career and conveniently your own.
我欣赏你的努力，卡索小姐，但我还是拒绝
I admire the effort, Ms. Castle, but I have to decline.
不过你倒挺会穿衣服的
You get points for style, though.
我不敢相信皮特干的好事
I can't believe Pete did this.
有些人天生伟大 有些人被动地卷入其中，苦苦挣扎
Some men are born to greatness, others are dragged into it, kicking and screaming.
克拉克？怎么回事？你为何要参选？
Clark? What's going on? Why are you running?
你从未对学生会表现出兴趣
You've never shown interest in student government.
别紧张，只是个恶作剧，皮特提名我的
Don't worry, it's just a gag. Pete nominated me.
- 那你会退选？ - 对
-So you're taking your name off the ballot? -Yeah.
很好，因为这次选举太重要了，不能沦为笑话
Well, good, because this election is way too important to turn into a joke.
有佛丽丝搅和就够乱的了
It's bad enough with Felice.
我听说她要找乐队搞餐会 搞一个选举前的狂欢
I hear she's throwing a pre-election bash with a band and catering.
她想像买名牌包包一样买下这次选举吗！
She is trying to buy this election like one of her Prada bags!
还真是神经质
Talk about tightly wound.
克罗伊，我虽没打算过，但如果我参加 你觉得会不会当选？
Not that I'm planning to, but if I ran, you think I'd have a shot?
会啊，只要我能当选啦啦队长
Yeah, right after I'm elected head cheerleader.
克拉克・肯特，竞选主席？
Clark Kent for president?
别担心，我明天就退出
Oh, don't worry, I'm pulling my name out tomorrow.
- 我倒认为这个想法非常棒 - 是吗？
-I think this is a terrific idea. -You do?
你总说没有机会表现，因为橄榄球不能参加…
You always say that you don't get a chance to shine because football is off-limits...
- …或许这次是你的机会 - 我以为你会不同意
-...maybe this is your opportunity. -I assumed you'd say no.
- 竞选学生会如此公开隆重 - 但不需要你使用超能力…
-Student government is such a public thing. -It doesn't require you to use your gifts...
…并且这你完全可以自主的校园活动
...and it's a school activity you can make your own.
怎么了，儿子？ 看起来你对这件事不是很乐意啊
Hey, what's the matter, son? You don't look too happy about this.
Hey-- Hey.
我平常都是尽量远离聚光灯
I've always tried to stay out of the spotlight.
我们没有一定要你去竞选
Well, nobody's saying you have to run.
你可以退出，但是要记住 一旦你习惯了放弃，可能这辈子都改不了
You can quit if you want, but remember, quitting's a very hard habit to break.
别给我压力
No pressure.
这个地方真是…
Wow, the place is....
空荡荡？
Empty?
没人？
Deserted?
很闲？
Vacant?
我想找一个比较委婉的说法 不过的确…
Well, I was searching for a euphemism to say that, but...yeah.
自从开张，另家咖啡馆就一直挤兑我们
The Beanery's tried to put us out of business since we opened.
我尝试过优惠券，降价，还有广告…
I have tried coupons, price cuts, even ads in the Ledger...
…但依然没什么改善，照这样下去 一个月就要关门大吉了
...so far nothing's worked. At this rate, we'll have to close the doors in a month.
跟莱克斯谈过吗？ 他是投资者，肯定能帮上忙
Have you spoken to Lex? He's an investor, I'm sure he can help.
他很反常，特别沉默
He's been uncharacteristically silent.
况且，这是我自己的战斗 输赢全在自己，我一定要赢
Besides, this is my battle to win or lose, and I am determined to win.
说起这个，我听说你也有场仗要打
Speaking of which, I hear you've got a battle of your own on your hands.
是选举，不过我没打算正式参选
Oh, yeah, the election. I'm not really running.
太可惜了，我觉得你会是个不错的主席
That's too bad. I think you'd make a great class president.
- 真的么？ - 当然了
-Really? -Yeah.
你很诚实，人们信任你 你有与生俱来的正义感
You're honest, people trust you. And you have this innate sense of justice.
当有人受到不公正的待遇时 我能从你脸上看出有多么不满
I can see it on your face how upset you get when you think somebody's being mistreated.
- 你真的这么认为么？  -是
-You see all that in me? -Yes, I do.
克拉克.肯特竞选主席
Clark Kent for president.
你怎么知道我参加竞选？
How'd you know I was running?
在镇上时，有人放到我挡风玻璃上的
I found this on my windshield in town.
帮我竞选那位干事有点头脑发热
I have an overzealous campaign manager.
没发现你还有从政的抱负
I didn't realize you had political aspirations.
没有，只是觉得自己可以做点成绩
I don't. I just figured I could make a difference.
你过来是为竞选筹捐的吗？
Did you swing by for a campaign contribution?
其实，我想问你是否知道塔龙的情况
Actually, I was wondering if you knew about the Talon.
你是说过去两周一直没有生意？
You mean the fact that it's been empty the last two weeks?
你会帮拉娜么？她已经用尽了办法
Do you plan on helping Lana out? She's tried everything.
其实她做得很不错
She's doing an admirable job.
- 如果塔龙歇业了… - 克拉克…
-lf the Talon goes under.... -Clark...
…我不会去补贴个一直赔钱的买卖 塔龙必须得自寻出路
...I won't subsidize a money-losing operation. The Talon has to find its own feet.
你至少可以去看看，表示下支持
Well, you could at least stop by and show some solidarity.
看，你已经开始为选民谋福利了
See? You're already working for your constituents.
需要些建议么？
You want some advice?
我认为你需要一个更好的竞选口号
I think you need a better slogan.
所有人都用过这个口号， 包括我
Everybody's used this one, including me.
- 你竞选过学生会？ - 一次
-You ran for student office. -Once.
- 但是我的动机不是很高尚 - 赢了么？
-But my aspirations weren't very noble. -Did you win?
当然
Of course.
有什么建议么？
Do you have any tips?
你不需要我的办法 用你自己的方法就可以胜出
You don't need my methods. You'll win on your own terms.
竞争很残酷
Competition's pretty stiff.
好好斗争不会有错…记住…
There's nothing wrong with a good fight. Remember...
…明日之星都需要今天的打拼
...the man of tomorrow is forged by his battles today.
我能用你那句话吗？ 用“明日之星”来作为我的竞选口号？
Could I use that? I mean, "the man of tomorrow," for my slogan?
尽管用
Knock yourself out.
（克拉克・肯特，明日之星）
"克拉克・肯特，明日之星” 有点太狂妄了吧，你不觉得么？
"Clark Kent, man of tomorrow." Kind of presumptuous, don't you think?
- 我喜欢 - 还以为你准备退出了
-I like it. -I thought you were bagging the election.
我改变心意了
I had a change of heart.
“明日之星”，真是抢眼
"Man of tomorrow." Very catchy.
谢谢，也谢谢你的鼓励
Thank you. And thank you for the encouragement.
我投你一票
You've got my vote.
我可以在塔龙举行选举聚会 顺便帮你招揽些人
I could have my election rally at the Talon, help bring people by.
太好了，有消息来找我
That sounds great. You know where to find me.
- 再见，拉娜 - 再见
-Bye, Lana. -Bye.
你是因为拉娜才参加竞选，难怪呢？
You're running because of Lana. Why am I not surprised?
我参加竞选，是因为我觉得我能干好
I'm running because I think I can do a good job.
- 好吧，克拉克，随便你了 - 你知道么，皮特对我有信心，拉娜也是
-All right, Clark, whatever. -Pete has faith in me and so does Lana.
- 有趣的是，你没有支持我 - 告诉我你的立场所在？
-It's interesting that you don't. -What do you stand for?
我坚持事实，正义，还有其他的
I stand for truth, justice and other stuff.
具体点，比如在某些重要问题上的观点？
You wanna be a little more specific, tell me where you stand on the issues?
- 你想谈论什么问题？ - 比如削减文艺预算的计划…
-What issues do you wanna talk about? -There's the plan to cut the arts budget...
…餐厅的食品营养过低 有关着装要求的争议…
...the appalling nutritional value of cafeteria meals, the dress code...
…还有学校搜查储物柜侵犯学生隐私问题
...and not to mention the student privacy issues with the locker searches.
慢点，我昨晚才决定参选
Slow down. I just decided to run last night.
我觉得“明日之星”得在今天就做出规划
Okay, well, I think the man of tomorrow needs to get a platform for today.
今天下午有一场女子排球比赛
Okay, there's a girls' volleyball game this afternoon.
你可以露个脸，拉些运动员的选票
You can make an appearance, court the jock vote.
星期五要空出来，有场音乐会 虽然演出很差，但你出现的时候…
Keep Friday clear, there's a band concert. They suck, but you've got to be seen...
- …要表现得像一名艺术爱好者 - 那我正经的主席规划会是怎样？
-...as a friend of the arts. -What about my platform?
谁在乎那个，大家喜欢你，就会投你票
Who cares? If people like you, they'll vote for you.
- 演讲时我该说些什么？ - 不知道，我不懂演讲的事
-What am I gonna say in my speech? -I don't know. I don't do speeches.
午饭见，我们可以在餐厅拉选票
See you at lunch. We can canvass the cafeteria.
他们以为自己是谁啊
Who do they think they are?
停下！
Stop!
现在不行，我有事要做
Not now. I have work to do.
（小镇高中火炬报）
克罗伊，有时间帮我们贴些海报么？
Any chance you could help us hang some posters?
皮特说如果我名字到处贴满，就肯定能赢
Pete's convinced if he puts my name on enough wall space, I'll win.
作一名公正的新闻人员，我正在做蜜蜂的报道
Besides needing to be an impartial member of the fourth estate, I'm doing my bee story.
环保中心有什么新的收获？
C.E.P. find anything new?
蜂群并不是从正常的栖息地迁来的
The swarms didn't migrate from any of their usual places.
本州所有的养蜂人都发现他们的蜂巢空了
Beekeepers all over the state have found their hives empty.
所有蜂群就像突然消失了
It's like the colonies just up and left.
这很奇怪，蜜蜂是群居性动物 通常不会轻易离开自己的巢穴
That's weird. Bees are followers. They wouldn't desert their hive without reason.
我妈妈对探索频道很着迷
My mom's addicted to Discovery Channel.
- 主席规划进行得怎么样了？ - 还没有开始做
-So how goes the platform? -I haven't started working on it yet.
一直忙着和人见面，周末也被邀参加派对
I've been so busy meeting people. I even got invited to parties this weekend.
不敢相信，区区一天时间 就让你为了人气而妥协了
I can't believe it took one day for you to be compromised by the lure of popularity.
我当选之后记得提醒我帮你拉赞助
Remind me to pull your funding after I'm elected.
说起这个，最新一版的在哪儿？
Speaking of which, where's the latest edition?
别，别，别！还没有校对完呢
No, no, no! I'm not done proofing it yet.
你最好别看，还没完工！
You shouldn't be looking at it yet. It's not done!
怕什么，我一直在校正你的标点问题
Come on, I've been correcting your comma issues since your first laptop.
（支持保罗参选）
- 你支持保罗？ - 克拉克，我必须要客观
-You endorsed Paul? -Clark, I had to be objective.
保罗还未退出，他秋天就会回来
Paul's still in the race, and he'll be back by fall.
你这么积极参加是好事…
It's great that you're all gung-ho and slogany now...
…但都是因为皮特的恶作剧
...but the truth is, you only ran because Pete suckered you into it.
保罗在正经问题上的立场很清楚 这点比你强
Paul has a clear stance on issues you have yet to articulate.
- 这跟个人关系要分开 - 我知道的，克罗伊
-It's nothing personal. -I understand, Chloe.
（本周拿铁半价）
伙计们，竞选游说的休息？
Hey, guys. Taking a break from the campaign trail?
很惊奇学校里有那么多我不认识的人
It's amazing how many people at school I don't know.
稍做休息，想试试你的半价套餐
This is a pit stop. Wanted to take advantage of your two-for-one deal.
这招再不行，只能找露胸女服务员了
Figure that's the last step before I institute topless waitressing.
好吧，那我希望这招不行
Well, here's to hoping it fails miserably.
- 看来你有顾客了 - 是惠特尼逼他们来的
-It looks like you have customers. -They're here because Whitney forced them.
路过另家咖啡馆，他们好像人挺多
Yeah, I passed by the Beanery. They're kind of busy.
那老板过来，说他就是要搞垮我们
The owner stopped by. He said he's made it his mission to run this place into the ground.
然后他还敢告诉我 跟个人关系无关，只是生意
Then he had the nerve to tell me that it wasn't personal, just business.
怎么40岁以上的人都喜欢引用《教父》？
Why does everyone over 40 quote The Godfather?
不知道，但真的很烦人
I don't know, but it's really annoying.
- 竞选的事怎么样了？ - 真是个很大的挑战
-So how's political life treating you? -It's definitely a challenge.
- 关键时候才看出谁是真朋友 - 演讲稿准备怎么样了？
-It shows you who your real friends are. -How's your speech going?
- 还没开始写呢 - 说不定我能帮你
-I haven't started writing it yet. -Maybe I could help you with that.
- 明天过来，我们一起写 - 真的？
-Come by tomorrow. We can work on it. -Really?
真是太棒了，你确定有空么？
That would be great. You sure you have enough time?
看看就知道了
Look around.
除非惠特尼逼着整个球队来 要么，我就应该有空
Unless Whitney can coerce the baseball team, I think I can squeeze you in.
很高兴看到生意有起色
Glad to see business is booming.
连老顾客都不来，生意当然难做
It's hard when even your regular customers blow you off.
我没有不理这边，我有注意到情况如何
I haven't been blowing you off. I've had my eye on the situation.
- 等着看我失败呢 - 大多数新人的生意都不会成功
-Waiting for me to fail. -Most new ventures don't make it.
要做好失败的准备
Prepare yourself for that possibility.
- 我以为你不喜欢输 - 我是不喜欢
-I thought you didn't like to lose. -I don't.
但是这不是我的战争
But it's not my fight.
- 作为投资者，必须知道何时放弃 - 你觉得我该怎么做？
-You have to know when to cut your losses. -So, what do you suggest I do?
那家咖啡店挑起了战争 如果你想生存，就要创新
The Beanery declared war. If you wanna hold on to this place, get creative.
要愿意做些不干净行为
Be willing to get your hands dirty.
不要担心，我不是让你干违法的事
Don't worry, I'm not suggesting anything illegal.
用《教父》的话来说，“该上床了”
To quote The Godfather, "It's time to go to the mattresses."
那部电影该被免费频道禁播
That movie should be banned from basic cable.
不要问
Don't ask.
好吧，拜
All right. Bye.
佛丽丝，我能和你说句话么？
Felice, can I talk to you a minute?
你还有55秒钟，说吧
You've got 55 seconds left. Go.
我做了个决定
I've made a decision.
你要退出吧
You're planning on dropping out.
不是，我觉得你该退出
No, I've decided you need to drop out.
相信我，这是不可能的
Trust me, that's not gonna happen.
你还没听说吧，我是领先者
In case you haven't heard, I'm the front-runner.
因为男人根本认不出最好的候选人
That's because these drones wouldn't know a qualified candidate if they saw one.
小地方就是会这样
That's the problem with this place.
就像是一个蜂窝有两个蜂后
It's like a hive with two queens.
如果你懂点自然常识，就知道总有一个失败
Well, if you knew anything about nature, you'd realize one always goes down.
知道么，你真是个怪人
You know what? You're a freak.
好吧，随你的便
Okay, have it your way.
但记住，我已经跟你心平气和地说过
But just remember, I did ask nicely.
- 盖比，今天最让我舒服的就是你 - 谢谢你，卢瑟先生
-Gabby, you're the best part of my day. -Thank you, Mr. Luthor.
- 你不是盖比 - 她今天不能来了
-You're not Gabby. -She couldn't make it.
你最好现在就离开，卡索小姐
Now would be a good time for you to leave, Ms. Castle.
人们总是服从你？
Do people always do what you say?
有什么不对吗？
Is that unusual?
我记得你说你欣赏坚持不懈
I thought you said you appreciated persistence.
我现在做得不好吗？
Besides, aren't I doing a good job?
你很幸运
Lucky for you.
花了很久才弄清楚什么能吸引你…
It took a while to figure out what would tempt you...
…我恍然大悟
...and then it hit me.
报纸封面照片比不上那句话重要…
It's not your picture on the Journal cover so much as the words...
…大写的“长江后浪推前浪”
..."Son Outshines Father" in the caption.
我做得怎么样？
How am I doing?
往下一点
A little lower.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
编辑许诺，如果搞定我，就给你专栏
Your editor promised you your own column if you land me.
- 那你能想象我会多感激你了 - 我觉得我能
-You can imagine how appreciative I'd be. -I think I can.
告诉我，莱克斯，我的机会超过50%了…
Tell me, Lex, would you say my chances are above-average...
…还是没有？
...or below?
就像我说的，我一直欣赏坚持不懈
Like I said, I always appreciate persistence.
你不会后悔的
You won't regret this.
还不是时候，凯瑟小姐
Not yet, Ms. Castle.
我付了一小时的帐
I paid for an hour.
佛丽丝・钱德勒，怎么了？
Felice Chandler, what's the problem?
给克拉克投票
Vote for Clark.
我一直以为和陌生人打交道会很难 其实还挺有意思的
I thought meeting people would be the worst part, but it's actually kind of fun.
我很高兴你这么觉得 因为根据我的午餐调查…
I'm glad you feel that way, because according to my latest lunchtime poll...
…你进展很不错
...you've got a shot.
你们好
Hey.
你好
进展怎么样？
How's it going?
只要回答“无意见”，她就不能断章取义了
Just answer "no comment." That way she can't misquote you.
- 你听说佛丽丝的事了么？ - 我刚去过医疗处
-You hear about Felice? -Yeah, I was just at the medical center.
她比保罗伤得更严重，正处于昏迷状态
She was stung way worse than Paul. She's in a coma.
一周内两个候选人被攻击了
Two candidates attacked in a week.
- 真是诡异的巧合 - 我觉得不是巧合吧
-It's a pretty freaky coincidence. -I think we've moved past coincidence.
你觉得发生了什么？
What do you think's going on?
记得去年萨莎被蜂群蜇伤的的意外吗？
Remember last year, Sasha's accident, when she was stung by a hive of bees?
你觉得因为那次，她就能控制蜜蜂？
You think because of that, she's controlling them?
只是个猜想
It's a theory.
这种猜想的思维跳跃度蛮大啊，不过我会调查下
Yeah, by several leaps and bounds, but I'll look into it.
这段时间，你也小心点
In the meantime, watch your back.
我刚听说佛丽丝的事
I just heard about Felice.
奇怪吧？
Weird, huh?
这种事往往是有原因的
Sometimes things just happen for a reason.
她可不像我这么在意这次选举
She didn't care about this election as much as me.
我也不太喜欢她，但她也不该受这个苦
She wasn't my favorite person, but no one deserves that.
好消息是，你不必继续竞选了
Well, the good news is, you don't have to run anymore.
佛丽丝退出了，你最好让我选中
With Felice gone, the best thing you can do is let me run things.
那么民主呢？大家有选择的权利
What about democracy? People should have freedom of choice.
听着，克拉克，我真的很需要这个
Look, Clark, I really need this.
我父母一定要让我赢，他们认为如果我输了…
My parents are riding me to win. They think if I lose...
…就不能去好大学 你有其他活动，但这次竞选是属于我的
...I won't get into a good college. You have other activities. This is my thing.
- 你为什么不退出？ - 对不起
-Why don't you just drop out? -I'm sorry.
我也有自己的原因想要赢
I have my own reasons to see this through.
你犯了一个错误
You're making a mistake.
听起来像是威胁
That sounded like a threat.
保罗和佛丽丝被蜜蜂攻击的事 难道你知道原因？
You wouldn't know how those bees wound up attacking Paul and Felice, would you?
你是在指控我吗，克拉克？
Are you accusing me of something, Clark?
只是觉得蜂群攻击两个竞选候选人 这种事不太寻常
I find it interesting that a swarm of bees would attack two candidates in this election.
我觉得背后有人在搞鬼
My thoughts are somebody's behind it.
好的开始
Good start.
我的垃圾桶里有三份草稿 但还想不出可以像主席那样说些什么
My trash bin has three drafts in it. Nothing I can come up with sounds presidential.
不用像主席一样，只要说出你的信仰
You don't have to sound presidential. Say what you believe.
- 写完这些，其余的就很简单了 - 那还是不太容易想啊
-Once you answer that, the rest is easy. -I've still got a lot of work to do, then.
没我这么不容易吧
Not as much as I have here.
我知道你处境艰难，但这已经做得很好了
I know you're having a tough time, but it's amazing what you've done with the place.
这只是个开始
This was just going to be the start.
我的梦想是还原老剧院
My dream was to restore the old theater completely.
还原那些放映机，屏幕，放老电影
The projector, the screen. Show old movies.
千万不要放《教父》
Just not The Godfather.
克拉克，快写演讲稿，必须要明确你的信仰
Come on, get back to the speech. You have to decide what you believe in.
我相信我的朋友和他们的梦想
I believe in my friends and their dreams.
如果他们的梦想破灭怎么办？
What if their dreams come crashing down around them?
拉娜，只要有我在，什么都不会破灭
Nothing's crashing down around you, Lana, not while I'm here.
谢谢你，克拉克
Thanks, Clark.
你听到了吗？
Did you hear that?
恩，从那里传来
Yeah, it was coming from over there.
还有那里
And there.
是什么?
What is it?
快点！进去！
Come on! Get in!
- 你呢？ - 趴下
-What about you? -Get down!
不敢相信你没被蛰到
I still can't believe you didn't get stung.
可能是我的皮厚
Guess I have tough skin.
保险申请会比被蜜蜂蛰还惨
The insurance forms are gonna hurt worse than the stinger.
不过我没事，多亏你
But I'm fine, thanks to you.
妮尔来了
There's Nell.
- 今晚我过得很开心 - 那以后要多经历些这种事
-I had a really nice time tonight. -Yeah, we should do this more often.
- 你确定没事吗？ - 很遗憾，我们没能写你的演讲稿
-You sure you're okay? -Sorry we didn't get further on your speech.
这是次要的事情，现在，我需要找到萨莎
That's the least of my worries. Right now, I need to find Sasha.
- 你觉得是她做的 - 恩
-Do you think she did this? -Yes.
只是不知道她怎么控制蜜蜂
I just don't know how she's controlling the bees.
- 你需要打给克罗伊 - 我们还是不怎么说话
-You need to call Chloe. -We're still not really talking.
你能相信吗？参选这事她不支持我
Can you believe she didn't endorse me?
如果我在她的立场，可能也会这么做
Well, if I were in her position, I probably would have done the same thing.
她只是客观地支持她觉得最有资格的人
She's just being objective. She endorsed the person she thought was most qualified.
- 没错，但… - 克拉克…
-Yeah, but still-- -Clark...
…你说过你相信你的朋友
...you said you believed in your friends.
她只是做了她觉得正确的事情
She only did what she thought was right.
克罗伊
Chloe.
拉娜告诉我了塔龙发生的事 谢谢打电话来
Lana told me about the Talon. Thanks for the call.
- 对不起 - 没关系，我不生气
-Sorry. -It's all right, I'm not mad.
克罗伊…
Chloe...
…关于你支持其他候选人的事，我不会放在心上
...I don't hold it against you. The endorsement, I mean.
谢谢，我本应该警告你的
Thanks. I could've warned you, though.
只是不喜欢跟你对立
I just don't like being in a fight with you.
我也不喜欢
Yeah, it wasn't my favorite part either.
去年起，我的生活都开始改变了 包括我父母…
Everything has changed in my life in the last year, with my parents...
…和拉娜
...with Lana.
唯一没变的就是你，我很高兴，克罗伊
The only thing constant has been you. I'm glad for that, Chloe.
我也是
Me too.
感觉像蜂蜜
This feels like honey.
蜂房里经常可以找到
Yeah, that's what you usually find in a hive.
不要告诉我，这全是萨莎干的
Don't tell me Sasha did all this.
不，是她的工蜂
No, her worker bees did.
- 她怎么控制它们的？ - 我猜她散发了一种叫做…
-How is she controlling them? -I think she's emitting something called...
…蜂后下颚信息素
...the queen mandibular pheromone.
是她掉进蜂窝时得到的能力？
She pick that up when she fell in the hive?
她被严重蛰伤
She was stung over a thousand times.
那些是非洲蜜蜂 因为她过敏，医生们对她没抱希望
They were Africanized bees. Doctors didn't hold out hope, because she was allergic.
他们怎么解释她奇迹般的复原？
How do they account for the miracle recovery?
他们不能，我也不能…
They don't. And neither could I...
…直到我发现事故发生在舒斯特峡谷
...until I found out the accident happened in Shuster's Gorge.
- 那是镇上最深的火山口 - 恩，你做过陨石统计
-That's the deepest crater in town. -Yeah. You do the meteorite math.
这些蜜蜂把她变成蜂后
The bees did something to make her their queen.
全州的蜜蜂都听她的指挥
All the bees in the state are taking a cue from her.
它们正帮她把斯摩维尔中学变成蜂窝
They're helping her make Smallville High her hive.
如果选举没按她的意愿，学校就有好看的了
If she doesn't like the way the vote goes, it won't be a pretty sight.
她也不会有好结果，蜜蜂只会忠心到一定程度
Neither will she. Bees are only loyal to a point.
一旦她失去控制，她的气味就会改变 那些蜜蜂也会知道
Once she loses control, her scent will change, and the bees will know.
它们不会高兴的
They won't be happy.
我以为你想找个私人的地方见面
Thought you wanted to meet somewhere private.
这家店最近就挺“私人”的
Lately this has been passing for that.
非常感谢你愿意来见我 我想多记下一些话
Thanks for agreeing to see me. I just want to get a few more quotes.
文章写得怎么样？
How's the article going?
人们会对你刮目相看
People are gonna see you in a whole new light.
是的，我确信他们会的
Yes, I bet they will.
- 我有幸读到初稿 - 你是如何得到的？
-I've had a chance to read the rough draft. -Where'd you get that?
我自有消息来源，这跟你的保证相差甚远
I have my sources. It's hardly the flattering expose you promised.
- 它很公平和真实 - 你扭曲了我的原话
-It's fair and accurate. -You twisted everything I said.
我的新闻学教授说过：“如果你想打败歌利亚…
My journalism professor says, "If you wanna bring down Goliath...
…最好知道他的致命弱点" 你的弱点是你太自我
...you better know his Achilles heel." Yours is your ego.
我发觉田纳西社区大学的都喜欢乱隐喻
I see they like to mix metaphors at East Tennessee Community College.
因为你查了我的背景，我就该害怕吗？
Am I supposed to be scared because you ran a background check on me?
- 我没有什么好隐瞒的 - 我父亲付了你多少钱？
-I have nothing to hide. -How much did my father pay you?
- 你真是想多了 - 不然还有什么原因让你如此对我？
-You really are paranoid. -Why else would you sandbag me?
我要坚持犀利的笔锋，并以此扬名
I plan on making a name for myself as a hard-hitting journalist...
恰巧你是个非常显眼的目标
...and you're a very visible target.
多少钱你才肯撤掉这篇文章？
What's it gonna take to make this article go away?
不同于你在询查报的走狗，我绝不出卖信仰
Unlike your whore at the Inquisitor, I'm not for sale.
再见，莱克斯
Goodbye, Lex.
多谢你让我第一个开刀
Thanks for being my first.
你想见我？
You wanted to see me?
我打算退出竞选
I've decided to drop out of the election.
我想应该第一个告诉你
I thought you should be the first to know.
很好，真高兴你终于想通了
Good. I'm glad you finally made the right decision.
那群学生想给你们投票，只能说明…
The fact that those people even considered voting for any of you guys just proves...
学校缺乏一个铁腕主席，那就是我
...that this school needs a strong leader. Now they'll have one.
为了胜出，你还真是不择手段
You'll do anything to make sure that happens...
甚至害你对手进医院
...including putting your opponents in the hospital.
我看出来了，你根本没想退出
I see what this is. You haven't dropped out at all.
- 我知道你是那些袭击的幕后主使 - 那又怎样
-I know you're behind the attacks. -So?
你又能怎样呢，克拉克？就算警方相信你
What are you going to do, Clark? Even if the police believe you...
他们也无法阻止我，没人能
...they can't stop me. No one can.
说不定我能
Try me.
你是为了这个？所以才引我过来
That's what you want, isn't it? That's why you lured me here.
你打算怎么办，克拉克？
What were you gonna do, Clark?
你在干吗？
What are you doing?
让你知道参政要做的牺牲
Teaching you that politics is all about sacrifice.
你要召它们去哪里？
Where are you sending them?
可能你皮糙肉厚，但你妈妈呢？
You may be thick-skinned, but what about your mother?
- 妈，你还好吗？ - 没事，谢谢
-Mom, you okay? -Yeah, thanks.
从未见过这么恐怖的蜜蜂袭击
I've never seen bees attack like that.
你猜它们去哪了？
Where do you think they went?
你怎么进来的？你妈妈呢？
How'd you get here? What about your mom?
我妈妈很好
My mom's fine.
都结束了，萨莎
It's over, Sasha.
还早呢，我还要作竞选演说
No, it's not. I still have a speech to make.
你要敢阻止我，我就在礼堂人群之前…
If you try and stop me, I'll be in front of an auditorium full of people...
- …你知道我会干什么 - 快停手吧
-...and you know what I can do to them. -You have to stop.
- 为竞选伤人不值得 - 我必须赢，克拉克
-No election is worth hurting people. -I have to win, Clark.
我父母说，人只分两类：领袖和庸民
My parents said there are two kinds of people in the world: leaders and followers.
他们期望我成为领袖，所以…
And they expect for me to be a leader. And that--
- 快让蜜蜂停下 - 我没叫它们回来
-You have to stop the bees. -I didn't tell them to come back.
怎么回事
Ow! What's happening?
快帮帮我！我对蜜蜂过敏！
You have to help me! I'm allergic to bees!
别让它们蛰死我
Don't let them kill me!
我送你去医院
Let's get you to a hospital.
（热烈庆贺新任主席:陈保罗）
难以置信，虽然佛丽丝和萨莎双双退出
I can't believe Felice and Sasha both dropped out and you still lost.
可你还是输了
- 我哪儿做错了？ - 你组织得很棒
-Where did I go wrong? -You ran a good campaign.
我们玩得嗨皮，交新朋友 得到的那些T恤一辈子穿不完
We had fun, met some new people, and we have enough T-shirts to last a lifetime.
- 不是给火炬报拍的吧 - 是给保罗的
-Please tell me that's not for the Torch. -It's for Paul.
他没法参加庆功宴，要我帮忙拍照
Since he couldn't attend his own victory party, he asked me to take pictures.
克罗伊，你支持他是对的，他最具资质
Chloe, you were right to endorse him. He was the more qualified candidate...
而我却只忙着拉票聚人气
...and I got caught up in the whole popularity rush.
虽然你支持的人赢了，也别太得意
Don't gloat just because your guy won.
赢了竞选输了朋友，又有何意义
Well, my candidate may have won, but my friend lost.
- 今晚我真为你骄傲，克拉克 - 为什么？
-I'm really proud of you tonight, Clark. -Why?
因为你看淡得失，败亦不馁
Because you're exhibiting dignity in the face of defeat.
这是伟大领袖的必备素质
It's the quality that all great leaders possess.
- 好热闹 - 以后常会这样的
-Nice crowd. -We'll be having more nights like this.
为什么这么肯定？
How can you be so sure?
这么说吧，我“上床了”
Let's just say I went to the mattresses.
明天看报纸第三版
Check out page three of the Ledger tomorrow.
能提前透露一下吗？
Can you give me a preview?
我得知，对手咖啡馆数次卫生违规
Apparently, a rival coffeehouse has had several health-department violations...
- 而他们一直试图掩饰 - 你怎么知道的？
-...they've been trying to cover up. -How'd you hear about that?
供货商告诉我的 克罗伊就请了一位记者朋友跟进
A vendor told me. So Chloe had a reporter friend look into it.
结果传言属实
And sure enough, it's true.
很有手腕，实在佩服
Very creative. I'm impressed.
竞选的事真遗憾
Hey, sorry about the election.
我爸说成败得失皆学问
My father says you learn more about yourself when you lose.
- 你学到了什么？ - 我不是搞政治的料
-What did you learn? -I'm not destined to be a politician.
政客要有双重人格
You need two different personalities.
要改变世界未必要当官，克拉克
You don't need to be an elected official to change the world, Clark.
- 你考虑过参政吗？ - 总有一天我要成为总统
-You ever thought about getting into politics? -Someday I'd like to be president.
这样的话，那句口号得还你了
In that case, you can have your slogan back.
没关系，你依然可以留着
It's okay, you can keep it.
卡索小姐
Ms. Castle...
多谢光临
...thank you for coming.
虽然已有所闻，但我要亲耳听你说说
I should probably know better, but I had to hear this.
为了保护双方，不介意我录下谈话吧
You won't mind if I record our conversation, for both of our protection?
请便
Feel free.
我请你来只是要恭喜你
I only asked you here to congratulate you.
说实话，我很折服
The truth is, I'm impressed.
很少有人能抓我现行
Few people have caught me with my guard down.
我猜猜，你要勒索我修改文章了吧
Let me guess. This is where you try and blackmail me to change my story?
我可不敢勒索你或要你改口
I wouldn't dream of blackmailing you or making you change a word.
我爸常说，无人议论之日，气数已尽之时
My father says it's when they stop talking about you that you should worry.
- 那我们没什么谈的了 - 不过话说回来
-Then I guess we're settled. -On the other hand...
你们报社总监位子近来出现空缺
...it turns out there's an opening for managing editor at the Journal.
我在那里工作
I work there.
- 如果有空缺，我肯定知道 - 我们认识的人不同
-lf there was an opening, I would know. -We don't know the same people.
你可以继续激浊扬清，保持犀利的笔锋
You could run your fair and balanced article word-for-word if you'd like.
也可以迈步走向总编办公室
Or you could show up to work tomorrow and walk into a corner office.
- 你想选择哪个？ - 有什么条件？
-The choice is yours. -What's the catch?
没有，或许有一个
No catch. Well, maybe one.
如果再有人勒索你，你就有所忌讳了
If someone ever tries to blackmail you, now you'll have something to hide.
真不知道你们父子俩哪个更毒
I don't know if you're better or worse than your father.
他发现你毙稿子的时候，会怎么说？
What will you say when he sees you killed the article?
- 谁说是他主使的？ - 省省吧，卡索女士
-Who says he's behind it? -Please, Ms. Castle...
我没侮辱你的智商，你也别侮辱我的
...l've never insulted your intelligence, don't insult mine.
我会说，不是我不做，是另有诱惑难以拒绝
I'll tell him I got an offer I couldn't refuse.
竞选总部撤掉啦？
Packing up campaign headquarters?
是啊，变回谷仓了
Yeah, it's back to just being a barn.
抱歉在塔龙没说上话，人太多了
Sorry we couldn't talk more at the Talon. It was packed.
那样挺好
It looked better that way.
- 我觉得挺好 - 只是…
-I'd assume that was a good thing. -It is. It's just....
我有点后悔对那家店使阴招
I'm not sure I liked what I did, playing dirty with the Beanery.
或许耍手段不是你的性格
Maybe the mattress isn't for you.
不成功便成仁，我必须做出选择
I had to choose between doing the right thing and being successful.
奇怪的是，使卑鄙手段我还挺开心
The weird part is, I kind of enjoyed being underhanded.
拉娜・郎堕入黑暗面？谁曾想到呢？
Lana Lang seduced by the dark side? Who would've thunk?
别担心，咱都未能幸免
Don't worry, we all get caught up.
我一心追求人气，连竞选的本意都忘了
I got so caught up in the popularity thing I almost forgot why I ran.
写演讲稿了吗？
Did you ever finish your speech?
写完了，但没人会听了
Yeah. Not that anyone will ever hear it.
- 我要听 - 什么时候？
-I could hear it. -Yeah? When?
就现在
Now.
- 现在？ - 是啊
-Right now? -Yes, Clark.
演讲！演讲！演讲！
Speech, speech, speech!
大家认为班级主席都无所作为，我不认同
Nobody thinks that a class president can make a difference, but I disagree.
如果想改变世界，需要从我做起
If we want to change the world, first we have to change ourselves.
我父亲常说，成败得失皆学问
My father always says that you learn life lessons whether you win or lose...
所以，希望尊敬的竞选伙伴能够与我携手…
...so I hope that my worthy running mates will work alongside me....